[{"category":"英検1級","question":"Implement means","correct_answer":"to begin to do or use","incorrect_answers":["to move or control something with your hands or by machine","to speak to a person or group","to manage the operation of something, such as a company or governemnt"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Undergo' means","correct_answer":"to experience or endure","incorrect_answers":["to make or build something","to speak to a person or group","to introduce a leader into a job or position with a ceremony"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Manipulate' means","correct_answer":"to move or control something with your hands or by machine","incorrect_answers":["to begin to do or use","to manage the operation of something, such as a company or governemnt","to make a bill officially become part of law"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Address' means","correct_answer":"to speak to a person or group","incorrect_answers":["to make a bill officially become part of law","to organize or plan something that is complicated","to introduce a leader into a job or position with a ceremony"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Fabricate' means","correct_answer":"to make or build something","incorrect_answers":["to organize or plan something that is complicated","made as an exact copy of something else","to experience or endure"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Administer' means","correct_answer":"to manage the operation of something, such as a company or governemnt","incorrect_answers":["to move or control something with your hands or by machine","to begin to do or use","made as an exact copy of something else"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Enact' means","correct_answer":"to make a bill officially become part of law","incorrect_answers":["to make or build something","to experience or endure","to manage the operation of something, such as a company or governemnt"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Duplicate' means","correct_answer":"made as an exact copy of something else","incorrect_answers":["to introduce a leader into a job or position with a ceremony","to speak to a person or group","to make or build something"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Orchestrate' means","correct_answer":"to organize or plan something that is complicated","incorrect_answers":["to experience or endure","to move or control something with your hands or by machine","to begin to do or use"]},{"category":"英検1級","question":"Inaugurate' means","correct_answer":"to introduce a leader into a job or position with a ceremony","incorrect_answers":["to speak to a person or group","to move or control something with your hands or by machine","to make or build something"]}]